Thank you for watching!
Let's get closer to each other in futsal & gatch time!
Yay!
- It's good! - That's what I'm talking about!
What do you value as an artist?
Don't overdress.
To keep on sparkling all the time.
I was thinking about all the things I could kiss-cut and talk about, and then I didn't say anything.
I've got some serious worries and irritations in there.
In the afternoon, we're all deciding on a dream.
The dream is...
problem
Next.
Let's go in order.
that's so, isn't it
problem
I don't know what's troubling me.
Questions about your concerns
What are some of the problems you can't talk about with other members of your group?
There are six.
I wonder.
It's not uncommon for Ryoga to take commentary shots.
What is required
You're always taking comments in between shots.
That means we are all in the same boat, right?
So Ryoga does all the work, including taking comments.
that (something or someone distant from the speaker, close to the listener)
This is like a member assignment, where Ryoga does all the talking and who does the talking.
I'm going to take these comments in between, and then I'll send you the script.
I'd like you to assign the members at the right time, and then I'm standing here in front of the camera, and I'm like, "Okay, I'm going to take the picture now.
I'm trying to decide what to do with the timing, and you're telling me to go ahead and do it.
Why are you being sent here? That's one of the reasons, isn't it?
Ryoga says, "That's your job, so do it.
But it's not like the leader is supposed to do it, so it's hard to say.
I mean, it's not as bad as it sounds, but I'm already in front of the camera.
Standing there, who's this, who's that, who's going to talk, who's going to do what.
It's like... It's a long story.
I think it's very ambiguous to take commentary shots.
It's like, "Hey, we're going, we're going, we're going, we're going, we're going!
I'm seriously worried and annoyed.
That's a serious one. I can't solve that one.
Because stiffs aren't the worst of the worst.
And then there's the way to tangle with the 10 below.
The real one came... Kashiwagi-san, right?
Haru Kashiwagi, who has been a back-up dancer for you guys.
Is that how it is?
I can't say that they seem to be having a good time doing it.
I'm too far away from them to care.
Haru is a solid girl, too.
He's very considerate.
I feel that, too.
I knew if I gave you 10, you wouldn't even know what I was thinking.
But it's solid, of course.
I just thought it would be a good idea to do it anyway.
I can't do it anymore.
I can't do words or anything.
I'm gonna give you something.
The other day, I gave him some chocolate that I really liked.
He looked so happy.
He's pretty smitten with me.
That's when I feel joy.
I have a little bit of a problem with that.
That ain't the same member.
It's a problem that I don't feel I have enough to tell the members about.
I'm getting a little confused about the distance between me and Haru.
You were originally a dancer.
What was your relationship?
I'm already a full junior.
also
He was so cute. He was like, "Don't be nervous, Spring, just do your best.
We had a drama together once in Fukuoka, a long time ago.
Like, Oku plays the third best role and Spring is on the same team, the soccer team.
It was soccer, too, and there was the same scene, but we were doing it in a normal way.
Afterwards, we talked about going out to eat, and I took Mochi with me.
Knights, I lost my wallet. I lost my wallet.
Go with her to the police station, make some calls, do some stuff.
Then one woman found me.
I ended up coming back with it, and miraculously, I was able to go.
I thought you might have forgotten that favor.
What's it like these days?
Like, "Good morning." Like, "Good morning."
When in doubt, say something like, "Good morning.
Like, "Good morning."
You're on a roll.
That's right.
Moreover, Hult had something to comment on the other day.
I've got something to say, too...
I was thinking things like, "Would it be okay if I spoke out of turn?"
He didn't say much.
Lately, the distance...
You used to come here all the time.
What, Hurt is all grown up now?
I don't know if you're on a roll or not.
You've been called out, Hal.
Are you watching? They're talking about you.
I thought I'd dare to say it here on YouTube.
I'm probably the first person to tell you about the wallet.
He says he's been with the police before.
Okay, next. Last.
I think I'll go dream.
I don't know, questions about dreams
What made you decide to become an idol of this industry?
What was your dream at that time?
I am...
I was not interested in show business, and then they gave me a skirt and I joined.
I started going to lessons at Ebidan with a guy named Jun Muto from the Genji Department.
I was in the prawn corps a little while before him, and he asked me to join the dragon corps.
That's when I went to Big Bang's concert.
I like Big Bang. I've been going there for a long time.
I've never seen a live performance before.
Of course, it's cool, and it's a great way to see how much excitement you can bring to the stage.
I guess that's when I had a clear idea of what I wanted to achieve after my debut.
I think it's around the third grade or something.
Did you have dreams when you weren't interested in the industry at the time?
I wanted to be a soccer player, but looking back now I think that probably wasn't possible.
You look really like me today, because I was the same way.
I mean, I wasn't even really interested in the world.
If anything, that idol thing didn't even really come through.
I liked it a lot. I went to Big Bang a lot.
I liked it. Just to watch it.
I never thought I'd do it.
When my manager asked me to try it.
And I thought, "What are you talking about?
Listen to the description.
Like, "I'm a main dancer and back-up vocalist group, and I'm a dancer who dances.
I thought, "No, I've never danced before.
Because I did it.
Is there anything that made you decide to go for it?
If you notice
Maybe when I find out.
There's not really a clear switch change here.
Oh, I see.
That's me. I was in the office before that.
Before entering the group
I was doing a little bit of acting before I joined the group.
I'm not sure how many of you know me these days.
I think people get the idea that it's like the group is doing it and they're doing the play.
Actually, sometimes the play comes first.
It's like a gradual process.
I guess it was a gradual process of taking it this way.
Dreams as an individual
I wonder.
I've never been to Golden, so I...
The play.
It's about time for a play.
I'd like to try harder, so...
Yes, Golden's.
I guess my goal is to star in a movie.
Golden's starring role
I like it, I like it.
I like that it's clear. It's easy to understand.
And that kind of thing.
I didn't know how to say this, but... it's a little bit loud.
Sano keeps putting words in my mouth.
he
Everyone is influenced to say it out loud.
I know, but sometimes you just don't want to say those things.
There's a time for that.
I know, I know. I don't want to put out anything too ambitious.
There's such a thing as a figure of speech.
I really think I should tell you. I've realized recently that I should tell you.
A.
My dream?
Oh, my dream.
That's what I wanted to hear, too. Personal.
I'm just looking at what's in front of me.
I'm not the type to focus. I can't think ahead.
Today is tomorrow. Tomorrow is the spirit.
I'm the type of person who doesn't want to think about tomorrow.
So the dream is
I guess I dream of not having it.
I see.
I'd like to do something like this with Super Express.
What is your dream as a group?
We also want to reach the dome. We want to reach Tokyo Dome.
I have, but personally, I don't think I have anything in particular.
I think I'll be in a music video for one of my back numbers.
You love it. You love it.
I've always dreamed of reaching the dome, and we've always said we'd like to.
I have a few more dreams for this year, and I have five dreams that we've all decided on.
First, arena tours I've only been to one arena and I want to do an arena tour.
Also, someone needs to be a drummer or do a commercial and sing the theme song.
I want to make a variety crown variety.
I want to have a hit song.
Climbing Mt. Fuji What's the last one? Climbing Mt. Fuji. If five of us climb Mt.
something
Ushizaki, Sano and others have always said it's a good idea.
Uh-oh.
I don't know. We've been through a lot together.
Beyond that, the top of the summit.
There are a few of that type.
Well, I'm hoping to make it this year.
Isn't it a wonderful dream?
First of all, isn't that it?
Fuji, so we'll start from Mt.
I think you should go.
Gradually. I knew it. You should go gradually.
Suddenly, right?
Sano might go out of nowhere.
Yes, you look strong.
Well, I'll see you next time, I guess.
Climbing Mt. Takao
I climbed Mt. Takao for Mt.
Will you go out with me?
No, I won't go out with you.
why?
Impossible.
Please go out with me.
Good, good dream.
Let's go for it.
Let's do our best. We both are.
I still have a long way to go.
Let's work hard for each other.
You've got a good story to tell.
Thank you very much.
I don't know...
deeply
Was I able to talk to you?
(sentence end) indicates emphasis, agreement, request for confirmation, etc.
tolerable
I kind of learned more about 10.
I feel like the percentage is going up a lot.
by the way
I'm up from 30.
about what percentage
Yeah, it went pretty well.
decar
tolerable
Good for you.
I don't know. I'll tell you what.
WHEREAS.
From the staff.
I've been entrusted with something.
see you, see you, see you
Wait. You can't just give this away for free.
Lifting rally, just the two of us.
If you can do it 10 times
I'd like to challenge you to present a corruption case.
I received this from a staff member.
I see
Do you want to win? No?
Patterns of not doing?
And I thought we were going to decide together. I'm making the decision?
That's right.
There's another pattern that doesn't separate the winners from the winners.
Then I'll take it home, won't I?
No kidding?
I'll do it then.
in the meantime
I wonder who they're both enthusiastic about. No, ten times, but...
I think it's a little bit difficult even for regular soccer players, even for active players.
Yeah, maybe if you were a normal middle schooler in high school.
If they were good, they could do it. Well, they could do it.
No, seriously, it's on me. It's on me.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
But let's do it. Let's do it. It's a one-shot deal.
A one-shot deal? Of course it is!
What? It's a one-shot deal.
Really? One shot. I told you first.
Here we go. Start getting ready.
Three, two, one.
stray arrow
Hey, you.
It's not me. I'm looking.
You.
Not me.
vigorously
I liked your first touch.
One more time, one more time, one more time.
sorry
I'm sorry to all the fans who really just can't help themselves.
One more time.
Just one more time, please. Sorry.
I'm sorry. Now that you mention it, there is such a thing as comedy.
now, now (used in calming people down)
Coming.
Hey, hey, hey.
Oh. Oh, sorry.
Wait. All of you.
ohhhhhh!
Thank you for your hard work.
Yay!
No, it's cool!
I got 10!
Here it comes!
Here it is!
All right, all right, all right.
Yay!
Thank you!
I liked his persistence at the end.
Well, that's great.
You've been over the chute.
Amazing!!!
Okay, okay, okay, I could do it 10 times!
It was great to even see the volley of guns.
So I'm a little out of breath, and I apologize.
This time, we are pleased to say that we have successfully obtained a meal ticket.
I don't remember the title anymore, but it's something about something that makes you want to do something.
I'd like to end on a positive note. How did it go? Distance.
What about gun-wise? Does it feel like it's shrunk?
I think it's great to learn more about Tiger.
You really didn't know what he was like.
I've grown quite seriously fond of it.
serious (not capricious or flirtatious)
I wonder what he's going to say.
I only saw him as a fan.
That one man... male male male
I thought he was a very nice person.
We'd love to hear from you.
I wish I could invite you to a game or something.
No, it's great.
I got shot in the heart with a volley at the end.
I've reached 150%!
Got it!
Great. Looking forward to your meal.
I'm looking forward to it. Just keep me posted.
please
So, two of us, not two of us, you know...
Yawata-ku, Yawata-ku, Yawata-ku, Yawata-ku, Yawata-ku, Yawata-ku.
Gachi-Talk Dialogue and futsal, over and out.
I'm doing the first part of the driving talk on your YouTube channel.
Please check them out as well.
It's over. It's over.
Please click the "Good Button" button and subscribe to our channel.
bye-bye